(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-29T01:34:02.090954",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
お気に召すまま
[Title: As You Like It]
淡々と言葉を吐いた
Spoke words detachedly,
あんな思い出に泣いたのは
crying over those memories...
今日で終わりにするかい
shall we put an end to that today?
1, 2の合図を待って
Waiting for the 1, 2 signal,
ユーアンドミー手を取り合ったのは
you and I holding hands
僕の勇気ある行動 フェイズ
was my courageous phase of action.
立ち止まらないでいいんだからね
It's okay not to stand still, you know.
空々しいな この人生
How empty this life feels!
出来ないなんて言わないでね 言わないでね
Don't say you can't do it, don't say it!
今更なんて言わないでね
Don't say it's too late now.
僕らいま さあさあ 輪になって
Now then, let's form a circle
回り始める
and start spinning.
段々嫌になって でも好きになる
Bit by bit I come to hate it, but then love it.
ねぇねぇ分かんないや 自分会議も
Hey, I don't get it, even this meeting with myself.
どんどん中に寄って でも離れてく
Steadily closing in, yet pulling away.
パッパッ 音に乗って 踊り始める
Quickly riding the beat and starting to dance.
散々嫌になって でも好きになる
Wretchedly coming to hate it, but then loving it.
ねぇねぇ分かんないや この先もずっと
Hey, I don't get it, now and forever...
僕の心をシェイクシェイク イエイ
Shake, shake my heart, yeah!
大正解なんてないのさ
There is no ultimate right answer.
じゃあ一体どこに向かえば物語は終わりますか
So where on earth do we head for the story to end?
1, 2の合図を待って
Waiting for the 1, 2 signal,
ユーアンドミー手が触れ合ったのは
you and I touching hands
僕の勇気ある行動 フェイズ
was my courageous phase of action.
畏まったって意味ないんだって
Being formal is completely meaningless.
恥ずかしがった夢にバイバイです
Saying goodbye to embarrassed dreams.
この先ずっとよろしくね よろしくね
Please treat me well from now on, treat me well!
君といま さあさあ 交わって
With you now, come on, intersecting,
目を逸らし合う
we avert our eyes from each other.
段々嫌になって でも好きになる
Bit by bit I come to hate it, but then love it.
ねぇねぇ分かんないや 自分会議も
Hey, I don't get it, even this meeting with myself.
どんどん様になって 崩れ落ちてく
Steadily taking shape, then crumbling apart.
パッパッ 触れる前に 消えてしまうの
Quickly, before I can touch it, disappearing.
散々嫌になって でも好きになる
Wretchedly coming to hate it, but then loving it.
ねぇねぇ分かんないや この先もずっと
Hey, I don't get it, now and forever...
分かり合えるまで僕たちは
Until we can understand each other, we...
今更なんて言わないでね
Don't say it's too late now.
僕らいま さあさあ 輪になって
Now then, let's form a circle
回り始める
and start spinning.
段々嫌になって でも好きになる
Bit by bit I come to hate it, but then love it.
ねぇねぇ分かんないや 自分会議も
Hey, I don't get it, even this meeting with myself.
どんどん中に寄って でも離れてく
Steadily closing in, yet pulling away.
パッパッ 音に乗って 踊り始める
Quickly riding the beat and starting to dance.
散々嫌になって でも好きになる
Wretchedly coming to hate it, but then loving it.
ねぇねぇ分かんないや この先もずっと
Hey, I don't get it, now and forever...
僕の心をシェイクシェイク イエイ
Shake, shake my heart, yeah!
Whoa!
Oh my God! Did you see us? We're so cute!
All four of us are so cute together!
Now, this is real content! Yeah, we should do...
This is where the money's at! It's... the money's in the concert!
This is where the money's at! The money's in the concert!
It's so nice to see everyone. More concerts! If only there was a concert that was coming up...
It's so nice to see everyone. More concerts! If only there was a concert coming up...
Ah, if only... if only there were tickets available right now for a concert.
Serendipity... I don't know where that word came from.
Wait, don't we invite even more people?
But if we invite more people, it won't be a concert anymore, because when there's more people, they start fighting.
You mean drama? Drama!
When you get too many girls in a room, drama happens!
But that does sell! People like seeing girls fight!
Sometimes there's just too many girls, you know? And yeah, and sometimes they just can't get along.
But that makes for good television. Let's content farm them.
FOLLOWING UP ON THE HOLOLIVE-ENIANS
LOS ANGELES
GINA'S CONDO
Oh my God, girl. If you want to hang out with us, you have to step up your bag game. Like, where do you even get your bag from? It looks bootleg.
You don't even recognize the bag I carried today?
Oh, next time we gotta take you to Bonel.
I own that company. What? You own Bonel?
I own the sister branch. Oh my God!
Oh my God, what are you cooking?
Oh, it's my newest recipe. It's a zero-calorie... Oh, shit!
It's a zero-calorie...
Oh my God! Oh, shit! Oh my God, what the...?
What happened?
Are you gonna pick that up?
Don't tell me what to do.
You literally threw it on the ground.
No, I didn't! You literally did! You can't accidentally throw something on the ground!
No, I didn't! You literally did! You can'accidentally throw something on the ground!
No, I didn't. You put it there. I put it there? You put your ass in my stupid kitchen, you bitch!
You absolute...! I did not do that!
You literally did that! You always make shit up! I wanted to do that, bitch!
Is this happening right now? Bijou, did you see her do that? Did you see that? Oh yeah, I saw that, sister! I saw you throw the frying pan down!
I saw you throw... No, I didn't! You sneezed!
Yeah, so I was making this totally delicious zero-calorie option dinner for everyone...
...because I know that everyone needs to lose a little weight for the party tomorrow.
And I just can't believe that she would do such a thing. Have you seen Céline? She's a total fucking bitch.
That food is gonna be nasty, and you know it.
She's always on these like health trips, but it doesn't do anything for her figure.
Come, come here! Don't tell me what to do! You're not my mom!
Look! Look at it! You threw that on the ground!
I've never seen that in my entire life! You've never seen that in your entire life?!
Did you get this for me for Christmas?
I would never get you something for Christmas!
What? You got it for me for Christmas!
You always do this! Someone hold me back! Hold me back!
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Leave her! Leave my friend alone! It's okay, it's okay, don't cry, you're gonna ruin your makeup!
Oh, you're so dramatic!
How dare you frame me! She's crazy! Did you... Shut the fuck up!
Who even are you? I don't know why the fuck I'm here!
I was just here to like promote my music...
...and like, all these, you know, really rich girls here... I'm so honored to be here, honestly.
But I don't know what the fuck went on. Like, what the fuck?
I think it's the water. There's something in the water.
I don't even know why IRene was here.
Who invited her?
She's sexy.
Why are you always so dramatic?
Me, dramatic?
Why do you always make shit up?
You live for the drama!
You are fake! You are fake!
The only thing about me that's fake is my tits!
Yeah, her tits are fake.
I would know. I paid for them.
Well, I was really insecure about my chest, so, you know, I got it.
You know, daddy paid for... No.
Wait, was it Gigi? Oh my God, I forgot about that.
I owe her. She's the best.
It's fine. Are you okay?
I'm not okay!
Breathe, girl, breathe.
Did you see what she did to me?
I saw.
That was unbelievable. Our food that I was looking forward to...
I was making a new low calorie option!
I was making a new low-calorie option!
Like, you should stop acting like that, you know. How old are you?
Wait, wait, excuse me? Excuse me?
I wasn't talking to her! Excuse me!
Get off me! Get off me!
Shut up! Shut up!
Oh my God, Bijou always has my back, girl.
I know she'll throw down with me.
Are you getting my good side?
Make sure you get the right angle.
This is for TV, right? Yeah, take me out.
Anyway...
Cecilia is a bitch.
I don't know what kind of problems she has with my girl Gigi,
but if she continues with this, we're gonna have to throw hands.
She better catch me outside, how about that, if you know what I mean.
I think she needs a wake-up call.
Bijou is such a follower. She doesn't have a single thought in that empty head of hers.
If you were to take her head and rattle it, it would sound like a baby rattle.
You guys are so loud. We're gonna get a noise complaint,
and it's gonna be so embarrassing for you because this is the...
The only noise complaint we'll get is when you're in your bedroom!
What? What does that mean?
In her bedroom! You know what?
Well, at least this apartment isn't under my name, so you're gonna get in trouble!
I will send you to jail!
My daddy's a lawyer!
You know what? My daddy owns your daddy!
My daddy might be under your daddy, but...
...he's a lawyer!
I think your daddy is under my daddy in more ways than one.
Do you see what she's doing to me, Bijou?
I saw, girl.
Oh, so you have a problem with dramatic, Nerissa?
You're so...
You're so dramatic! Oh my God! You!
Don't touch her ever again, you understand?
Oh my God, who do you think you are?
Get away!
She did not!
She pushed me!
Raora threw herself on the floor. I saw it happen.
She's just so dramatic.
She fell like garbage!
Well, she's such a pick-me girl.
That Raora, what a pick-me.
Kind of a bitch.
I pick her, though.
Have you seen her thunder thighs?
Dang, I wanna bite that. Don't tell her, though.
Cut that out! Cut that out!
Quella cagna... Da me non avrà più quella cagna...
That bitch... She won't get anything else from me, that bitch...
Sempre ancora quella cagna...
Always that bitch again...
Se mi tocca di nuovo, io non sarò fatto più! Basta, ho finito!
If she touches me again, it won't be good anymore! Enough, I'm done!
Raora's so sweet. She always got my back.
Sometimes she falls down though, but you know, it helps for my cause, so it's okay.
Shut up! You have a problem, and you're a danger to society!
I am a danger?!
She's down! She's down!
Watch out, watch out! You're gonna ruin her outfit!
Ow! Stop!
I mean, come on, Gigi's... Gigi's dying!
How dare you! Stop touching each other!
This is getting a little too far, I think.
I got you, girl. I got you. Get up! Get up!
Ow, now you're ruining my outfit!
Anyway, guys, I'm kind of hungry. Do you want...
I want food! I came here for food and networking!
I was making a new low calorie recipe that I... 'cause you really need to slim down.
I was making a new low-calorie recipe that I... 'cause you really need to slim down.
I was looking out for you!
If you're cooking, I guess everyone's going to lose their appetite.
I'm not hungry anymore!
I thought Gigi was trained by a Michelin chef!
I was!
No, she's just lying. She always makes up this shit.
Namaste! Namaste!
I can expect something so nutritious. It's really nutritious.
How dare you try to ruin our perfect five-star meal!
Well, it was really delicious, though.
Five stars!
You ruined Thanksgiving!
Well, you know what? She can do whatever she wants, and you are no one...
Well, I can say whatever...
I lied.
Leave her alone, Raora. Leave... Leave Biba alone.
So, what are we here for anyways?
Dinner! Dinner, guys! Dinner!
Do we get to actually eat?
Are we gonna eat? That's right!
We're gonna eat! Oh my god!
Anyways, I wanna go back to the kitchen and I'm gonna finish cooking.
Yeah, where you belong!
You little [bleep]!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hold, hold, hold me back off her! Oh, you better back off.
Animal abuse! Animal abuse!
Are you okay, girl? Girl, are you okay?
Just cause your dad is a lawyer doesn't mean you can do whatever...
The fork's not suing you!
Make me look good in the edit, okay?
Check out my album!
Mm... I feel like that was too many swear words.
I think they said too... there's too many beepings in there.
Yeah, it was almost like Morse code.
Or even censor "fuck"!
Or "shit"!
Ah... I just... I don't know...
Stop. I would never swear on your channel, by the way.
Yeah, you're so sweet. That's really nice of you. I feel like...
I would never fucking do that. That's so messed up of someone to do.
Yeah, I just... I just wish they would have edited that out, you know? I'm really uncomfortable right now.
I'm only five minutes old! I'm not allowed to hear those words!
I'm just really scared. It's also... I don't think we're gonna make any money out of that because it's not gonna be allowed to be aired.
Demonetize our channel!
What if... what if we have a show, but instead of like real people, it's scripted?
Oh, yeah! Then we can make sure that there's no curse words, and we'll take them all out!
Yeah! Yeah! It can still be drama, right?
Mm, yeah, just no cursing.
No cursing, please!
Please no cursing on our channel!
HALF A FORTNITE AWAY FROM DEATH
[Title: HALF A FORTNITE AWAY FROM DEATH]
PREVIOUSLY ON:
HALF A FORTNITE AWAY FROM DEATH - THE TALE OF BEAVER AND THINKER.
TWO UNLIKELY SURVIVORS FIND EACH OTHER IN THE MIDDLE OF THE APOCALYPSE, AND ALTHOUGH WARY, THEY'VE COME TO FIND COMFORT IN EACH OTHER'S PRESENCE.
HAUNTED BY THEIR PAST, AFRAID OF A FUTURE THAT MAY NEVER COME, WILL THEY EVER BE ABLE TO OVERCOME THEIR STRUGGLES AND REACH MUTUAL UNDERSTANDING IN A DYING WORLD?
FOR MORE INFORMATION, PLEASE WATCH SEASON 1 AIRED ON JULY 3, 2024.
So, have you thought about it?
You just... you always say things, but in reality...
I love you.
No, you love your wife!
She's dead now.
You don't even remember!
Even if she's dead, that doesn't mean that she's not there anymore. And I've been thinking about it because I'm the Thinker.
What are you even?
I'm the Beaver.
Oh man, if I was a beaver, I'd be eating so good right now.
Because I have wood! Look at my wood! Check it out!
Pretty impressive wood.
So you won't want for nothing.
But you love your wife! You don't understand!
But still, over the past seven days...
...that we've learned to survive...
You just want me for my body.
You're not interested in my mind! I'm the Thinker!
No, I want you for your mind! I want you!
No, no, you have to understand! You're wrong!
No! Please! It doesn't have to be like this!
Look at my wood! Check out my wood! Look at my wood!
No, I don't want to look at your wood! I don't want your wood!
I don't want your wood!
But you'll be so full!
Ew! Ew! Put that away! Ew!
Look at my wood! You don't even want to see my mind!
Aah! Skeleton!
A skeleton! Run away! Run away! I'll protect us!
I mean... I mean Beaver. I'm the Beaver. I'm not Gigi, I'm Beaver! I'm the Beaver!
Beaver, be careful!
Oh my god, where'd you get that weapon? I've never seen you use that before.
Yeah, I bought it from that one pawn shop owner, remember?
Oh yeah! That guy! With the one eye!
Was it Suami?
No.
Watch out! Watch out! I'm so scared! Watch out! So cool!
Oh my god, the skeleton! She's so cool! Woah! Woah! That bad ass skeleton!
Oh, she's just... Guys, it's too strong!
Oh, it's just so cool!
いつか君が 瞳に灯す 愛の光が
Someday, the light of love that you set aflame in your eyes
時を超えて
Will transcend time,
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を 確かにひとつ
And surely destroy one dream of this world that hurries to its ruin.
壊すだろう
Destroy it, it surely will.
躊躇いを飲み干して
Swallow down your hesitation.
君が望むモノは何？
What is it that you wish for?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
On the path of yearning as greedy as this,
儚い明日はあるの？
Will there be a transient tomorrow?
子供の頃夢に見てた
Like the ancient magic
古の魔法のように
That I dreamed of when I was young,
闇さえ砕く力で
With a power that can break through the darkness,
微笑む君に会いたい
I want to meet you and your smile.
怯えるこの手の中には
What I hold in these frightened hands of mine
手折られた花の勇気
Is courage made of handpicked flowers.
想いだけが頼る全て
My feelings alone are all that I rely upon,
光を呼び覚ます
A wish that will awaken the light...
願い
A wish...
いつか君も誰かの為に
Someday, you will also wish for great power
強い力を望むのだろう
For the sake of someone else, I suppose.
愛が胸を捉えた夜に
In the night when love captured your heart,
未知の言葉が生まれて来る
Yet unknown words are born.
迷わずに行けるなら
If I can go on without losing my way,
心が砕けてもいいわ
I don't mind if my heart is broken to pieces.
いつも目の前の哀しみに
I want a spell that can let me fight
立ち向かう為の 呪文が欲しい
Against the sorrow that is always in front of my eyes.
君はまだ夢見る記憶
You are a memory that continues to dream.
私は眠らない明日
I am the sleepless tomorrow.
二人が出会う奇跡を
I will move forward in order to attain
勝ち取る為に進むわ
The miracle of the two of us meeting.
怯えるこの手の中には
What I hold in these frightened hands of mine
手折られた花の刃
Is a sword of handpicked flowers.
想いだけが生きる全て
My feelings alone are all that I live for,
心に振りかざす
A wish that I brandish within my heart...
願い
A wish...
囚われた太陽の輝く
When I used to like books about strange lands
不思議の国の本が好きだった頃
Illuminated by captive suns,
願いはきっと叶うと
I believed the fairy tales
教えるお伽話を 信じた
That taught us that wishes would surely come true.
静かに咲き乱れていた
Gently, magic from ancient times
古の魔法優しく
Bloomed wildly in silence.
世界を変える力が
"The power to change the world
その手にあると囁く
Lies in those hands of yours," it whispers.
終わらない夢を見よう
Let us have an unending dream.
君と行く時の中で
During this time I go through with you,
想いだけが生きる全て
My feelings alone are all that I live for.
命を作るのは
What will create my life
願い
Is this wish.
They brought them back to kill them off?!
They killed a main character! Like, it's not a big cast, it's literally just two characters!
I can't believe that you would have a finale of a show years ago, and then you would do a reunion episode to kill the main character!
It's so stupid!
Oh my god. Well...
These writers don't know what they're doing! That's not gonna make any sense!
We should trash this idea! This is a terrible idea! You know what? Not my canon!
Not my canon!
This is not my show!
No, no. This is just a cash grab! I hate it!
Okay, okay.
You know what else is a cash grab?
What? What?
The AutoFister merchandise!
If only we could have someone here that can tell us about it!
Is this... Is this thing on? Oh okay, great.
Hey everyone! It's me, Mori Calliope from Hololive English Myth,
coming here to you today to ask you to please purchase this merchandise...
...dot dot dot...
...the AutoFister Net merch set! Ever wanted a Gremtomo keychain...
...or a Gimimi or Cemimi?
Or better yet, an acrylic stand with AutoFister on it??
Open parenthesis, noise of enthusiasm, close parenthesis.
Oh... Oh wow!
For the low, low price, 99.99 open bracket price will be beeped close bracket...
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry! Um...
I gotta do it again. This... This can be yours!
This can be yours!
And if you purchase now!! I will say this one super awesome word out loud!
Open bracket, pregnant silence, close bracket.
That's... That's two words.
Wait, no. Okay, I see what's... That's three words! I'm not saying that. Guys, did you check the script beforehand?
Oooh, this was a bad idea! This was a freaking bad idea! I don't know why I agreed to this!
League of Legends, thank you. And buy the merchandise.
Oh, wow! Thanks, Calli!
She loves us! She loves our merch!
Grow up! Nah mean?
Track Giga
劣等上等 BRING IT ON
Inferiority, Bring It On!
劣島上等 不眠日本
Inferior island, sleepless Japan!
劣等上等 BRING IT ON
Inferiority, Bring It On!
子供騙しのマセマティカ　威張り散らしたその態度　プライドすらないや
Childish math tricks, bossing everyone around without an ounce of pride.
ゴシップ崇拝　調子こきで　高みの見物ばかりじゃつまんねぇ
Worshipping gossip, acting cocky—watching safely from above is so boring!
ほらもっと　間違って上等　退屈に手をかけて
Come on, make more mistakes, put an end to this boredom!
こんなところじゃ終われない
It can't end in a place like this!
ぬるくて気が触れそう　ごっこ遊びも芝居もさよなら
It's so lukewarm I'm going crazy; goodbye to playing pretend and acting.
ずっとこのままなんてさ
Staying like this forever? No way!
ダッダッダ　あたし大人になる　酸いも甘いも噛み分けて今
Da-da-da, I'm growing up, tasting both the bitter and sweet now!
パッパッパ　変わる時代　悪いことばかりじゃないでしょう
Pa-pa-pa, changing times—it's not all bad, right?
過去も　罪も　罰も　すべて
The past, the sins, the punishments, all of it...
素手で　愛で　生き抜いてやり返すわ
I'll survive with bare hands and love, and pay it all back!
Yeah, 挑発 あたしたちは no doubt　緑のアイツにばっか構ってんね
Yeah, provocation—we're no doubt always paying attention to that green one!
さぁ burn up いつになったら貰える合格　赤ペン入れてよ どこがダメなんですか
Come on, burn up! When will I pass? Mark it with a red pen, what's wrong with it?
酒 女 金 ドラッグ Chillってaiight... 冗談じゃんブラックジョーク
Booze, women, money, drugs, chilling out, alright... Just kidding, black humor!
中指立てたくなるような事情　ありすぎて指が足りねぇから hands up and what's up 最低? 元々だろ bring it on
Too many situations make me wanna flip the bird, not enough fingers, so hands up and what's up! The worst? Always been, bring it on!
「まあまあ」なんか要らない　欲しがります死ぬまでは
I don't need "so-so"! I'll keep craving more until I die!
借金背負って街に投げキス
In debt to my ears, throwing kisses to the town,
見せつけろ パワーはここから
Show off! The power starts right here!
覚悟しとけよー ダダダダ
Get ready for this, da-da-da-da!
ぼくら大人になる カウントダウン
The countdown for us to grow up has begun.
狙い定め 痛い体感的に
Take aim! Painfully, instinctively,
燦々とかます じれったい
strike brilliantly! So frustrating!
誰も読めない先回り
Stepping ahead where no one can read us!
泣くの？伏すの？つれーの？すべてつれーの？
Are you crying? Sulking? Is it tough? Is it all so tough?
生きて生き抜いていくのよ
You gotta live and survive through it all!
Let's go!
ダッダッダッ くだらない
Da-da-da, so pointless!
言葉ばかりが譲れない
Nothing but unyielding words.
わかるか？あたしの美学
Do you get my aesthetics?
この場は承知の威勢
Showing off full well on this stage.
気の小石ひとつが
A single small pebble of spirit
切り札
turning into a trump card.
ガラガラタワー
Clattering tower,
一撃KO さらば！
one-hit KO, farewell!
Every otomo and every gremlin home, put your hands up!
こんなもんじゃない
It's not just this!
ダッダッダッ あたしよ
Da-da-da, it's me!
どんなになれる？清も濁も甘いも酸いも
What can I become? Purity, impurity, sweet and sour,
見分けて今
telling them apart now!
燦々交わるミライ
A brilliantly intersecting future,
遅いこともないわ
it's never too late,
わかるでしょ？
you understand, right?
期待 期待 待ってくれない
Expectations won't wait.
連れてってあげる 生き抜いて頂戴
I'll take you along, so please survive!
Ah... 愛ある時代！
Ah... an era filled with love!
それでは皆様、お先にバイキャ！
Well then everyone, bye-bye for now!
わかりました！
Understood!
Are you thinking...
...what I'm thinking?
I think I am!
Oh my God! We have to bring this...
Write this down! Write this down right now!
We're going to the suit!
Oh my God, they're gonna love this!
They're gonna love it!
They're gonna love us! They love us!
This is bad.
I'm going to give up on my dreams.
Never give up on your dreams.
Really?
Yeah. I feel like you had half a good idea...
...and you had half a good idea, too.
And together... that's a whole good idea.
We'll get the funding one day.
Thank you very much everyone that helped us work on all these shows together.
Thank you to all our beautiful, wonderful guests!
And thank you to you, grems and otomos...
...at home, watching us today during our TV show.
Please sign our petition and look at the credits!
And don't forget there's something else coming up in just a few minutes!
Very special, right after this! So don't change the channel!
Don't change the channel just yet! Put down that remote!
Gun to your head, put it down right now!
Put down the remote right now! There's something really cool coming up right after this!
The Autofister Network! 3D LIVE!